<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>STS Innovation, Inc.</title>
    <link>http://sts-innovation.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on STS Innovation, Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <atom:link href="http://sts-innovation.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sts-innovation.com/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sts-innovation.com/en/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sts-innovation.com/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sts-innovation.com/en/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sts-innovation.com/en/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sts-innovation.com/en/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;main class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h1 class=&#34;col-xs-12 text-center&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                The following policies and disclaimers are applicable to all Internet media managed by STS Innovation, Inc. (hereinafter called STS INNOVATION). You are considered to have agreed to them when using the site.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;No warranties&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                This website is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied.  STS INNOVATION makes no representations or warranties in relation to this website or the information and materials provided on this website. 
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, STS INNOVATION does not warrant that:
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;this website will be constantly available, or available at all; or&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;the information on this website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Nothing on this website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind. If you require advice in relation to any legal, financial or medical matter you should consult an appropriate professional.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Limitations of liability&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                STS INNOVATION will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contact, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this website:
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;to the extent that the website is provided free-of-charge, for any direct loss;&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;for any indirect, special or consequential loss; or&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;for any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated savings, loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information or data.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                These limitations of liability apply even if STS INNOVATION has been expressly advised of the potential loss.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Exceptions&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit STS INNOVATION&#39;S liability in respect of any:
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;death or personal injury caused by STS INNOVATION&#39;S negligence;&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on the part of STS INNOVATION; or&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for STS INNOVATION to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Reasonableness&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                By using this website, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this website disclaimer are reasonable. 
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this website.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Other parties&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                You accept that, as a limited liability entity, STS INNOVATION has an interest in limiting the personal liability of its officers and employees.  You agree that you will not bring any claim personally against STS INNOVATION&#39;S officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the website.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Without prejudice to the foregoing paragraph, you agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this website disclaimer will protect STS INNOVATION&#39;S officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors as well as STS INNOVATION.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Unenforceable provisions&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                If any provision of this website disclaimer is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that will not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this website disclaimer.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Credit&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com.
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/main&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sts-innovation.com/en/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sts-innovation.com/en/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;main class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h1 class=&#34;col-xs-12 text-center&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;What information do we collect?&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;What do we use your information for?&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                To process transactions
                &lt;br&gt;
                Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;How do we protect your information? &lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Do we use cookies? &lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                We do not use cookies.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Do we disclose any information to outside parties? &lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Third party links&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Online Privacy Policy Only &lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;Your Consent&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/main&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>